Anastasia Andreeva

Software Quality Assurance Test Engineer

Profile

5+ years experience of Software Quality Assurance using most modern practices and approaches strong experience in Manual testing and Test Automation using JavaScript and Cypress testing tool, Jest framework. Experienced in Software Development Life Cycle, Test Development Life Cycle and design execution of all work products and deliverables (Test Methodologies Agile, Test Plan, Test design, Scenarios, Test cases, Test Reports, Defect Report).

Employment History

Software Test Engineer at Yandex, Portland, OR

August 2021 — Present

- Performed Black/Grey box Manual Functional Testing on Web, including Regression. Performed End-to-End testing.
- Involved in writing and implementing Test Cases, Test Scenarios, and Test Scripts in accordance with Business Requirements.
- Used JavaScript language and Cypress testing tool for scripting.
- Designed, executed and maintained automated test cases for regression testing.
- Involved in validating the API with Postman tool and create the Continuous Integration mechanism.
- Developed responsive web applications sound knowledge on HTML, CSS, Java Script, React for Front-End.
- Collaborated with Business Analysts, Developers and UI/UX designers to design test cases for testing web products.

Software Test Engineer at Epam Systems, Moscow

August 2017 — August 2021

- Performed manual functional web testing including regression and exploratory.
- Performed build acceptance regression test before each release of the application.
- Performed API testing using Postman.
- Created and maintained test cases and scenarios, based on customer requirements.
- Reported issues using the internal bug-tracking system and provided bugs verification.
- Analyzed business requirements and suggested improvements to the product features.
- Collaborated with software development team members to establish immediate resolution of identified issues.

Achievements:

 Reduced development costs by 20% by carrying out continuous assessment of project requirements and setting out priorities right.

Contacts

Portland, OR, 97239 Willing to relocate 2099225266

anastasiia.andreeva1890@gmail.com

Links

GitHub Web Site Linkedin

Skills

Functional Testing

Automation Testing

API Testing

Test Cases

Bug Reports

Cypress

Agile Methodology

HTML

CSS

JavaScript

Jest

React.js

Git

Node.js

Mongo DB

Express.js

JSON

- Successful completion of several projects ahead of schedule, which reduced costs by 10%.
- After the successful completion of several projects by our team, the customer signed a contract for a longer cooperation.

Education

Certificate, Junior Software Testing Education, Moscow May 2015 - July 2015

Diploma, Mechanical Engineering College, Karpinsk, Russia September 2005 — July 2009